Goodbye, Buffalo Crush!
What's the speed of a car that takes 8 hours to travel 456 km?
57 kilometers per hour.
Hehehe...
How far does a plane flying at 340 meters per second travel over seven seconds?
2,380 meters.
Hehehe!
Homework done!
Jun. It's no use knowing the answers if you don't know how to solve the problems.
But you know time is money!
I'd really like to save time on doing homework so I can read more!
But... that's a comic book.
A comic book is still a book!
That's true.
Tell me. Would you like to read some of my comics sometime?
Aagh!
Dad! I told you to knock first!
I did.
But... who were you talking to?
Uh, haha... I was just talking to myself.
Talking to yourself means that you are under a lot of stress.
You should know the Milky Way will be closed tomorrow.
So how about we go on a family road trip?
Yahoo! I'd love to!
Why does it feel as though things aren't going our way?
Can't you come up with some brilliant plan to steal the treasure of planet Machina?!
We already know where it is...
So why not launch a surprise attack?!
A surprise attack?
Yes! Or we could try taking the child's family hostage!
We only here for treasure.
Leave uninvolved humans out of this.
Hahaha! I see you have some loyalty in you!
If you have a better idea, why not share it with us, Buffalo Crush?
Me handle this.
Where are you off to now?!
Let him go!
A pirate always stays true to his word!
Me don't want her to get hurt.
Ugh... what's so fun about going on a road trip?
Shh! Be quiet!
I could get there way faster than a car!
Shhh!
Talking to yourself again?
Ahahaha! It's nothing!
He's starting to take after you.
Me?
You always do that when you're driving, haven't you noticed?
Ha, do I really?
What's the hurry?! You gotta go to the bathroom?! Why didn't you go earlier?! You're a terrible driver! What if something had happened?!
-See?
-So irresponsible!
Uh... excuse me?
Ooh, what a strange car!
Do you need something from them?
Uh, yeah...
I heard they're not home today.
They were all going on a trip to the Itar Plateau.
Itar... Plateau?
Thank you.
Itar Plateau, Itar Plateau...
They're in trouble!
Your call could not be connected. Please try again later.
Ugh! I'm bored!
If I knew it would be like this, I would've stayed home!
Jun.
Yeah?
Do you have... anything you want to tell me?
Uh... something to tell you, like...
Maybe something like any worries or secrets you may have.
You know, you can always tell me anything.
Uhh... haha...
Dad! I don't have any secrets.
Jun. Do you think we've been discovered?
There's no way.
I gotta use the restroom first. You guys go ahead.
Okay!
Woah! Haha!
How's the view? Glad you came?
Yeah!
I used to have worries at your age, too.
When I couldn't work things out,
-I would turn to nature to forget about them all.
-Where is this conversation going?
You're 12 and there are things you don't want to tell us.
But it's not right to tell lies. That would make your parents sad.
I-I would never lie to you guys, you know that.
Just a second.
Hello? Theo?
Jun! Bad news!
Buffalo Crush was at your place!
What?! Again?!
I think he's headed your way!
Huh? What's wrong?
Huh? Huh!
Hey, Jun!
Mom!
Jun!
Found you! Yaah!
Huh?
Please give back Machina's treasure!
You are... what treasure?
Your son have it. I beg you! Please!
Me owe miss Yuri my life!
Me don't want you getting hurt over this.
Mom!
Darling, what's going on?!
Well done, Buffalo Crush!
Black Hook!
Now. Take the Metal Breath from him!
Jun. Summon me now!
I can't!
If I do that, you'll be found out!
Small fry. I'm giving you 'til the count of three,
to hand over the treasure of planet Machina!
One.
What do I do? I can't summon them with my parents here. They'll find out everything!
Two...
I don't have a choice!
Three!
No!
Buffalo Crush?...
Told you, me get Machina treasure!
Do promise mean nothing to pirates?
If it means obtaining the Metal Breath, such promises are insignificant.
Jun!
Dad! Mom! I'm sorry! I'll explain everything later!
Jun! What are you doing?!
Metal Breath, pickup!
Shadow X, setup!
!
Step aside!
H-he summoned a robot!
Our son did that?!
Shadow X, blow them away with your Heli-Tornado!
Okay!
Heli-Tornado!
Quickly! Lower the sails!
You've made your last move.
Now it's my turn to blow you to smithereens!
Stop!
Me say it again.
You leave this to Buffalo Crush!
Have it your way, then.
Hurry up and take the Metal Breath!
We're leaving, Buster Gallon.
Of cou- Huh?
Where are you going?! Hold on, Black Hook!
That's Captain Black Hook! Captain!!
T-Thank you, Buffalo Crush...
Metal Breath...
is treasure from planet Machina.
It not yours to keep.
That's not true.
Blue Cop?
Jun is qualified to have it.
That is why I gave the Metal Breath, entrusted to me by Deus Machina, to Jun.
Qualified? How you know?
The fact that Jun is wearing the Metal Breath... is the proof.
I don't really get it... but it seems like other people can't wear this.
Me don't believe you...
Then how about a fight?
What?
Try to fight him! And you'll find out just how worthy Jun is!
I don't like violence...
but I'm ready to prove my friendship with the Metal Cardbots!
Okay.
We fight!
It's dangerous here. Please come with me.
We're staying with Jun.
We can't leave, we're his parents!
Now, now, this way please!
It's ok! You can watch from where it's safe.
Mega Trucker, setup!
Mega Trucker, Mega Power Tackle!
Finally! I was getting bored!
This is awesome! It's a battle of all brawn and no brains!
Wanna say that again?!
Not over yet!
Buffalo Vision!
A laser beam attack?! Not fair!
What is that green stuff?
That's...
Oh dear! It looks like his wound hasn't fully healed yet!
Thank you, Mom!
Mega Trucker, Mega Touchdown!
Mega Touchdown!
Let's finish this!
Dexter, setup!
Dexter, into the ground!
Hungry...
Dexter, aim for the Milky Way!
Spiral Ray!
Metal Cardbot, Change Up!
Buffalo Crush... sealed!
I hope this proves it for you.
Yahoo! A new subordinate!
Hey, we don't work that way, Shadow X!
Huh?
Are we really just going to leave him?!
He told us to leave it to him!
A pirate does not go back on his word!
Goodbye, Buffalo Crush!
Are you actually crying?
Shut up!
Mom, Dad...
I'm sorry I've been hiding this from you guys!
You don't have to be sorry.
Jun, we have known about the Metaca... I mean, the Metal Cardbots all along.
It's no surprise.
Eh???
You've been coming home late, your most treasured bike all smashed up...
It was all just too strange.
So we confronted Edo. And then asked him to tell us everything he knew!
So... he told us everything that's happened up 'til now.
Uh, there's this robot from the planet Machina called Blue Cop!-
Your mom and dad can see through everything.
And not just that... we know what else you've been hiding.
Uh oh...
So... you mean...
Do you have anything you want to tell me?
Maybe something like any worries or secrets you may have?
Was this what you were talking about in the car?!
Your scores have been really bad.
But what's worse is hiding them from us.
That makes me really sad.
I-I'm really sorry, Mom and Dad!